<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Exhibition on Story:Web</title>
    <link>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Exhibition on Story:Web</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 14:34:48 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://storyweb.info/exhibition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Idea #3</title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/idea3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:34:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/idea3/</guid>
      <description>People are already making and sharing short videos about environmental issues - including the 16-19 year old participants who worked with us.
But, if you are not already looking for these videos, how would you find them?
Many aspects of our lives have environmental impacts, which we sometimes don&amp;rsquo;t realise.
EnviroAds What if&amp;hellip;
When you’re looking at a website about something you’re interested in, a video appears in one of the advertising slots, Which explains an environmental issue relating to it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idea #2</title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/idea2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:34:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/idea2/</guid>
      <description>Museums have databases of their collections.
But some objects are described in more detail than others. And museum objects mean different things to different people.
Museum curators describe objects using special terms. But they don&amp;rsquo;t always mean the same to the rest of us or - sometimes - curators with different expertise.
SenseMaker What if&amp;hellip;
We &amp;lsquo;crowdsourced&amp;rsquo; the meaning of museum objects by asking people to describe objects? Perhaps as an online game?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idea #1</title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/idea1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:23:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/idea1/</guid>
      <description>Every museum object can be a starting point for a story.
Stories help us make sense of environmental issues like climate change, biodiversity loss, and food security.
But it can be hard to find an object to inspire your story.
Story Inspiration Station What if&amp;hellip;
A screen showed three objects at the push of a button, Either connected with an environmental issue or chosen at random. And you start a story inspired by one of these objects, That you can then share with others?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Objects</title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/objects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 14:35:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/objects/</guid>
      <description>Sensemaker Objects In the &amp;lsquo;What if?&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo; exhibition at the Great North Museum: Hancock, we asked you to describe three objects in three words. This is how the Museum&amp;rsquo;s keepers describe them. How well do the keeper&amp;rsquo;s descriptions match your words?
Object 1: The Whitburn Harpoon This harpoon was found on the shore at Whitburn. It was possibly washed up from the sea and is therefore, potentially, an object from Doggerland.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
