<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Story:Web</title>
    <link>http://storyweb.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Story:Web</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 14:35:22 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://storyweb.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Objects</title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/objects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 14:35:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/exhibition/objects/</guid>
      <description>Sensemaker Objects In the &amp;lsquo;What if?&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo; exhibition at the Great North Museum: Hancock, we asked you to describe three objects in three words. This is how the Museum&amp;rsquo;s keepers describe them. How well do the keeper&amp;rsquo;s descriptions match your words?
Object 1: The Whitburn Harpoon This harpoon was found on the shore at Whitburn. It was possibly washed up from the sea and is therefore, potentially, an object from Doggerland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop2</title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/blog/workshop2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 10:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/blog/workshop2/</guid>
      <description>We had another interesting second workshop with everyone this week. Previously, we’d explored the problems of having better conversations online about environmental issues and how objects from museum collection could play a part in bringing environmental issues to life. In this workshop, we began exploring how images and sounds shared online (with creative commons licences) and interactive technology could also help.
For creative commons images and sounds, we used websites to find photos, videos and sounds that related to the environmental issues everyone was interested in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop 1</title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/blog/workshop1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 19:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/blog/workshop1/</guid>
      <description>It was great to meet everyone in our first workshops at the end of January, where we explained the Story:Web co-design project further and how it might help us develop ideas for &amp;lsquo;museums of the future&amp;rsquo;. Before the workshop we&amp;rsquo;d asked everyone to find something online relating to an environmental issue they were concerned about. During the workshop we talked about these issues, which included deforestation, poaching, air and water pollution, the environmental impacts of energy generation, fast fashion and block-chain technology, and the often hidden plastics and pollutants in packaging and some musical instruments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/blog/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 16:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/blog/welcome/</guid>
      <description>If you are taking part in the Story:Web co-design workshops, thank you! (If not, you can find out how to take part here ). We&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing our progress here on the &amp;lsquo;blog. This post explains what we’ll be doing in the first workshop and gives you some simple tasks to do before it.
Before We Begin Once you know more about the project, you need to formally agree to take part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/storyweb/snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/storyweb/snippets/</guid>
      <description>Grey Seal Skull From the Natural Sciences Collection of the Great North Museum: Hancock This skull is from a Grey Seal and came from the Farne Islands off the coast of Northumberland, UK. Grey Seals are predators and eat between four and six percent of their body weight in one feeding per day. The diet consists of a large variety of fish and the occasional crustacean (lobsters, shrimps and prawns) and molluscs (squid).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story:Web</title>
      <link>http://storyweb.info/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://storyweb.info/home/</guid>
      <description>Making sense of global issues through museum collections, images, sounds, and personal experiences</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
